https://www.collectrussia.com/privacy.cfm

Order of the Badge of Honor
Orders of October Revolution, Friendship of Nations,
Badges of the Early Soviet Volunteer Organizations
Badges of OSOAVIAKhIM (Society to Support Aviation and Chemical Defense)
Soviet Parachute Jump and Airborne Troops Badges
Air Force Wings and Qualification Badges
Veteran Badges of Air Force and Air Defense Units and Schools
Soviet Railway Awards
Members of Supreme and Local Soviets (Government)
Copies of Soviet Badges
Generals and Admirals: Uniforms, Insignia & Accessories
Generals and
Admirals:
Visor Hats & Headgear
WW2 Era Officer and Enlisted Uniforms
Officer and Enlisted Visor Hats
Headgear (other than visor hats)
Sculptures and Bas Reliefs of Lenin & Stalin
Soviet Statuettes & Busts in Metal (Bronze and Silumin)
Soviet Porcelain Figurines
Propaganda Porcelain Vases, Plates, Plaques etc.
Books on Imperial Russian Medals & Badges
Books on Imperial Russian Uniforms, Edged Weapons & Militaria
Click to open new account
Price:
Contact CollectRussia
Atlantic Crossroads, Inc.
P.O. Box 144Tenafly, NJ 07670
U.S.A.
Phone: 201.567.8717
24-hour FAX: 201.567.6855
Email:Sales@CollectRussia.com
Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.collectrussia.com This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following: 1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. 2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. 3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. 4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. We do not send unsolicited emails. Should any changes be made to this privacy policy, we will post them here. Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website: Change/correct any data we have about you. Express any concern you have about our use of your data. Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 201 567 8717 or via email.
|
Home
|
Terms
|
Contact Us
|
How to Order
Collect Russia © 2004-2020, All Rights Reserved.
